NEDA PARVINI

nedaparvini1@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/neda-parvini-846356a8 nedaparvini.com

SUMMARY

Software programming computer engineer with more than 18 years of experience in graphic and web design. Knowledgeable in computer graphics, web programming and database. Languages I can speak are Farsi, English and Spanish. I am US permanent resident.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, ASP Classic, SQL Server, JavaScript, Python, Adobe Dreamweaver, Adobe Fireworks, MS Project/Excel, Visio, Corel Draw, Corel Photo paint, Corel PaintShop, Corel VideoStudio, Gif Animator.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Social media and Graphic Designer | Davis Sensory Institute (Davis, CA)

December 2019 - February 2020

- Social media and graphic designer
- · T-shirt designer

Volunteer at North Davis Elementary School (Davis, CA)

November 2018- March 2019

Freelance Web and Graphic Designer (Tehran, Iran)

March 2007- March 2018

Computer IT Companies and Consulting Engineer Companies (Tehran, Iran)

June 1994- March 2007

EDUCATION, AWARDS & CERTIFICATIONS

- Dynamic Website Makeover with PHP & MySQL Tehran Institute of Technology 2016, Tehran Iran
- CIW (Web Design and Development) ISIRAN Institute 2012, Tehran Iran

2010 Tohran Iran

Spanish Language – Albroz Institute -

2010, Tehran – Iran

Marco Comun II (Spanish Language) – Kish Institute of Science and Technology
JAVA/J2EE – Iran ACM (Association for Computing Machinery) Chapter

2009, Tehran – Iran 2005, Tehran – Iran

• English for Success – Renison College – University of Waterloo

2004, Ontario, Canada

B.S in Software Engineering/Programming – Azad University of Tehran

2002